If somebody's going to initiate a false
flag operation, it's almost always the
the Israelis. The Israelis are one of
these high-risisk, highreward kind of
countries. Most countries are not like
that. Most countries wouldn't take these
great risks, but the Israelis do, and
they do it as a matter of routine
policy. So, if there's going to be a
false flag, yeah, I would take a good
hard look at the Israelis.
>> Yeah. And I um the only one I know of is
there on the Amirati side during the war
there was a lot of skepticism or at
least I was told it was skepticism but
maybe further inside the the
administration maybe they even knew it's
Israel that some of these operations
were false flag. Israel was trying to
get the Gulf more involved in the war.
They wanted the Gulf to attack Iran. But
is there kind of level is there some
sort of leniency against false flag? For
example, if Israel conducts a false flag
against the UAE to drag them into the
war, it generally speaking, would the
UAE say this is a red line, they they
civil relations, they retaliate, is it
like a massive red line for them, an
escalatory step, or is it something
that's part of warfare? They accept it
like, "Hey, don't do this again," and
they do it back to them. Is that part of
just the way things are? It's kind of a
mix. Normally, what you would do is call
in the Israeli ambassador and say, "Stop
doing this." or they're going to there
are going to be prices to pay.
>> Bad boy
>> strongly worded letter. [laughter] We
will write a strongly worded letter. Um
but the thing is is you have to consider
all facets of the relationship. So for
the Amiratis in particular, this
relationship with Israel is lucrative.
It's opened up, you know, a new trading
partner really is what it comes down to.
And you know, everybody knows, I mean,
going back to the to the 70s,
um, all of the Arab countries in the
Gulf were buying Israeli fruit, for
example. What the Israelis would do is
they would harvest the fruit, send it to
Cypress, put it in new boxes that say
produce of Cypress, and then send it to
the Arab countries. Now, they don't have
to do the extra step, so it's cheaper,
you can buy more things. They've got
this economic relationship. The Saudis
are not there yet. The Kois are not
there yet. The Bahinis are kind of there
but aren't really comfortable with it.
The Godries aren't going to do it. And
the Omanis just want to be left alone. U
but uh but for the Emiratis, they have
to weigh the entire relationship. And
that's why maybe you you or I would go
to the Israelis and say enough is
enough. This is over the top. You're
trying to drag us into a war. This was a
false flag operation. We proved it.
We're severing relations or we're
expelling your ambassador. The Amiradis
wouldn't do that. The the relationship
is too
>> I have the Iron Dome here in the UAE.
>> Yeah, that's right.
>> They're screwed. And they depend they're
stuck to the US because they depend
heavily on the US dollar and that
system. And they're stuck with Israel
because they have the Iron Dome.
>> What a bad spot to be in.
>> Terrible.
Terrible. And they have a very robust,
at least Dubai does, a very robust U
trade with Iran. They always have. And
when I was with the Senate Foreign
Relations Committee 2009, I went to
Dubai just to talk to business leaders
about trade with Iran and they were
trading literally everything. Everything
from food to, you know, toner cartridges
to cars and everything in between. and
they were like, you know, we're not
gonna we're not going to stop trading.
This is our bread and butter.
>> Um, I'm just taking notes of things I
want to bring up in our conversation. I
um I'm actually going to bring up
something just about Israel's
capabilities. I uh remember speaking to
an official very very close to the Trump
administration. That was a few months
ago and that was a private discussion.
But I've spoken to others about this,
but this is probably the most the best
example. someone very very senior in the
administration and they gave me an
example of I asked a question just threw
it out there because that's a fun
question to ask you know we had a long
conversation and I said like you know do
you think the Israelis are you know are
listening to you are tracking you cuz
he's very involved in the region and
some of our listeners would know very
well and someone from his his seniority
I'm like the Israelis would never go
that far and then he's like Mario I gave
up on the Israelis and he gave me an
example I won't share here he gave me an
example where they were able to
intercept a call he was having with
another world leader and lo and behold A
few days or a few weeks later, we got
the report that Israel, that's actually
a good point to bring up with to ask
your thoughts on Israel was labeled as a
critical threat on the intelligence
level.
>> Critical threat for counter
intelligence.
>> Yeah. Along with Russia, China, Cuba,
and North Korea.
>> Yeah. Listen, this is not new. This is
decades long. I'll give you an example.
In on my very first day at the CIA,
we're briefed by the director of
security, right? You stand, you take
your oath, you swear to protect the
Constitution against all enemies,
domestic and foreign. You sit down, the
director comes and says, "Welcome to the
CIA." And then the head of HR, and then
this guy and that guy, and the chief of
security, and the chief of security
tells you essentially, you're going to
have to learn to keep your mouth shut.
Don't talk about work when you leave
this building. for example, don't ever
go to this first restaurant that's
that's right by the CIA because the
Russians think that we all eat there and
so it's all KGB, the whole restaurant.
I've never been to that restaurant. It's
a steakhouse. Jay Gilberts, I think it
name is. So, the Israelis are the same
way. There are Israeli spies everywhere,
hundreds of them, all over Washington.
Three weeks ago, the Defense
Intelligence Agency sent out an all
hands email warning every single
employee of DIA that Israeli espionage
against the US government is at an
all-time high right now. So, don't talk
about work outside the building.
But we just accept that. When I was on
the job for about 6 months,
there was a man in my office who was on
the phone, secure phone with a
counterpart overseas. Um, we used to
have these phones called STU3s. There
are Stews, STW 2Bs, and STE 3es. So,
they're secure phones, but they're not
permanent. You can you can move them.
So, you pick up the phone, you call the
number, you say, "Hi, it's John. Are you
ready for the call?" going secure and
then you press the encryption button and
the phone encrypts itself and then it's
it just sounds like gibberish to an
outside listener. So the problem with
stew 2bs and stew 3s is they'll
occasionally drop the call. So my my
colleague is talking to somebody
overseas and the conversation is going
both ways and the call drops and so he's
just waiting for to see if his colleague
comes back on and then he hears somebody
say Mosha did they hang up and then the
other voice says I don't know David
maybe they dropped the call and then
Moshe says okay they'll call back if
it's important
now what are we supposed to take from
that we're supposed to take that for
decades the Israelis have been
intercepting our calls, even secure
communications.
So, are they intercepting the president,
the vice president, the the secretary of
state or secretary of defense, the
national security adviser, all their
deputies, the jo the the members of the
joint chiefs of staff? Of course they
are. That's why they're ranked as
critical threat for counter
intelligence. And what's Congress's
response? Congress's response is to give
them an office at the Pentagon and at
the CIA with the National Defense
Authorization Act.
>> I wrote that section 224. I think they
changed the name.
>> Yes. [sighs]
>> I think it's 209 now. Something like
that.
>> Yeah,
>> they they they changed the name the
other day.
>> Um
why do you think the the administration
doesn't do anything about it? What a
>> That's easy.
>> That's easy. polit politics
politics. Um, Apac has spent so much
money in American politics at every
level, not just the federal level, but
state and now local levels, too, that
you don't dare challenge the Israeli
government. You don't dare do it because
they will primary you and they will
defeat you. And so if you want to
survive as an American politician, you
have to be utterly completely
pro-Israel. You can't say, no politician
is going to say, you know, the Israelis
are spying on us all over the United
States. They're embedded in our defense
contractors. Um they're on Capitol Hill
stealing our secrets, trying to
infiltrate the the CIA and the FBI and
the DIA. Nobody's going to say that. to
the point where, and you know this as
well as I do, an Israeli government uh
official who happens to be a a pedophile
is picked up by the local police in in
Las Vegas. And what do we do? Quick, get
him on a plane. Get him out of here. A
pedophile. We choose the Israeli
government over our own children.
And the American voters are supposed to
just accept that.
It's crazy how just you'd assume
considering how blatant it's been
recently, you'd assume that most people
know about this, but we'd be surprised
outside our circle of our audience, what
we watch, our algorithms, most people in
the US, otherwise Massie would have won.
>> Exactly right.
>> No money. There's no like no one can
spend enough money to, you know, to make
to make Osama bin Laden seem like a good
person cuz everyone knows Osama Badin is
a criminal. Okay, I'm trying to find an
example here. Um, but for some reason,
it's probably not the best comparison,
but I'm bad at thinking of examples, but
for some reason, this the the the how
Israel has hijacked the American system.
And again, good for Israel. They've been
so effective at it. Um,
>> it's been brilliant and it's taken
decades. I this was a very long-term
policy, a very long-term view to to
winning over the American political
establishment. They've been very
successful at it.
>> Yeah. But it's just for some reason like
if enough people know no money spent
would be able to turn people on Massie.
It just seems so obvious.
>> But they're so but they're so smart,
John. The Spain thing, if they're behind
the Morocco thing. I'm saying if just
cuz if I don't know for sure, but as I
looked at Jiala, look what happened with
Sanchez. All it takes is one call to the
king of Jordan who is very close to
Israel. He's part of the Abraham's
Accords. They do a lot of things
together.
>> Um supports I think he's one of the
first countries that accepted I think
Palestinians to immigrate into Morocco I
think.
>> Um so all it takes is Netanyahu and it
seems to call the king of Morocco, hey
we want you to ship tens of thousands of
people cuz it was coordinated. That's
indisputable.
>> Yeah. This doesn't happen by magic.
>> Exactly. We want you to ship them all to
those two cities, those two Spanish
cities, and we'll help you back in
Washington. And what do you get from
from Washington? You have different
members of Congress saying that these
places are part of Morocco, part of
Moroccan territory. The narrative has
been created. The bubble has been burst.
Now Morocco is going to begin the
process of trying to get those two
cities from Spain. Even if they fail,
that's kind of giving Spain the middle
finger.
>> I think that is exactly correct. That is
exactly correct. That's exactly what
happened.
>> Pretty damn scary. Um, okay. I want to
ask you about the um actually one last
question on the counter terrorism
counterterrorism
classification the critical threat. Um
has anything happened after that? Cuz I
heard about the news. It came out and
leaked nothing by the New York Times and
then not a peep and I'm waiting to see
what happens next. What do the
administrations do afterwards? What do
the intelligence agencies do afterwards?
I haven't heard anything. Not sure if
you know something.
>> No, you you really can't do anything
because it's a it's a political
decision. It's a policy decision. So, at
the CIA, uh, the CIA has something
called the the counter intelligence
center. So, its job is to work very
closely with the FBI to root out moles,
foreign intelligence officers burrowing
into the American government,
specifically to the American
intelligence system. Um, and you're
looking for Russians and Chinese and,
you know, the occasional Cuban or the
Iranians. Well, we know that the
Israelis have hundreds and hundreds of
spies all across America.
So, you refer the CIA will develop this
information. They'll refer it to the
FBI. And the FBI says, "Well, what can
we do?
We don't have the political
authorization to arrest these people or
even to disrupt them. And we know that
the Israelis aren't going to use it to
like, you know, bomb us or blow up
American cities or whatever. So it's not
like the, you know, the Chinese or the
Russians that mean us harm. So h just
let them get away with it. Now
any other country, let's let's just say
for the purpose of argument, let's make
one up. Let's say, you know, the
Netherlands is a critical threat for
counter intelligence. What would happen
at the CIA
is a policy would be implemented whereby
um
CIA
employees are not allowed to transit
Skipple airport in um in uh Amsterdam,
right? You just stay away stay away from
the airport. They're going to steal your
laptop. They're going to steal your
information. They're going to steal your
identity. It's going to be terrible. Um,
and then you back off with liaison
exchanges because they're going to be
trying to recruit the liaison officers.
Well, with the Israelis, we we do
literally nothing. Literally nothing. We
just let them get away with it and
invite them to the White House. And
again, the White House and merging
merging. Yeah. the the the the example
you've given of putting it giving them
an office in the Pentagon. What you're
referencing is section 224 now 209 or
whatever it is the merging of the US and
Israeli militaries.
>> Yes.
>> Like I I don't know what's next after
that is Netanyahu becoming the president
of the United States. I that's the only
thing left
>> there. There's there's one there's one
bit of hope one ray of hope. Netanyahu
has never gotten Netanyahu is the
longest serving prime minister in
Israeli history. he has never gotten
more than 27% of the vote because um
there are so many viable political
parties in in Israel. Now the the
political makeup of the country has
changed dramatically with the influx of
so many um ethnic Russians and
Ukrainians. So it's pushed the whole the
whole you know populist to the right and
that's why we have the likes of Bengavir
and Smotri and some of these other
extreme rightists. Uh but there's a real
possibility that in Israel's upcoming
elections, and I think they're in
October, uh that that there may be there
may be a movement among the populace to
say enough is enough. Now we're in this
war. There's no end to it. You look at
the polls in the United States and and
by a factor of 2 to1, Democrats uh are
now opposed to the Israelis and
Netanyahu in uh in the fight with u in
Gaza and opposed with equal numbers to
uh to the war in Iran. Um independents
are just as equally opposed to the
Israelis and Netanyahu. And now a
sizable minority of Republicans
are opposed to Israel and Netanyahu. So
what is what the Israeli government is
doing? It's backfiring and they need to
do something different and they may I
guess it's possible that they could
start doing something differently with
the next election.
>> Um what do you know about the Gulf? I
know we've talked about it has been
pretty long. The capabilities of the
Gulf. I think you'd know more about
their intelligence capabilities more
than their military capabilities. I'd
love your comments on both. But how
capable are they? How how and how
intertwined do you think they are with
the US? Can they walk away? Can they
survive without the US? And also maybe
you can comment on the Emirati Israeli
relationship. I think this is a pretty
pretty important development that we've
seen here. The the Amiratis really
doubled down on that alliance with the
Israelis. Not sure if that's still the
case now that the war is is uh has
shifted, but um I'd love to get your
thoughts on this. My information is
dated. I left the CIA 22 years ago, but
I can tell you that the that the Gulf
countries, the the countries of the GCC
have very very good intelligence
services. Um, very capable officers,
highly trained, multilingual,
great experience uh in countries all
around the world. I I worked very very
closely with almost every one of those
intelligence services and they were all
excellent. Now really the best are the
uh the Amiradis and the Gutaries.
They're all good but the Amiradis and
the Gutaris are the the best with the
the Amiradis being the best of the best.
The thing is is as as you allude to the
the Amirati relationship with uh with
Israel is very complicated
because it's multiaceted. It's it's
energy. It's defense. It's trade even
like I said food stuffs and clothing and
it's just very complicated. And so yes,
they doubled down on this relationship.
But the longer the ward drags on, the
more they have to be thinking, you know,
we should probably give them the back of
the hand in the next few days
>> and try to get him to back off. And uh
but then the most important question is
the one that you you posed last and that
is uh how does this end? I've been
saying from the beginning
to the surprise of no one that I think
the way this ends is we wake up one
morning and Donald Trump has posted on
Truth Social at 3:00 a.m. It's all over.
We win. They've capitulated.
>> Yeah, I was going to say that.
>> I'm bringing everybody. I obliterated
them. They've been obliterated.
Vaporized.
>> I've launched the greatest
has destroyed them last night. Exactly.
So, the greatest victory in the history
of victories,
>> you know, and I think that's how it's
going to end.
>> Yeah.
>> Because, as you rightly pointed out, we
don't really hear about the Israelis
anymore. I think they're done.
>> Yeah. That I I I put I thought of this
earlier today. I put out a poll saying,
"I can't believe it. They did it. The
Israelis dragged the US into this war
and stepped away. Now, just sitting
there watching, mission accomplished."
>> Yeah.
>> It's uh pretty wild.
>> Exactly.
Um you were talking about the uh the
capabilities of the Gulf uh security um
apparatus. You remind me of a story.
I've never shared this. So um I won't
mention which which uh which country it
is, but I had so I had someone from my
team, my my executive team talking to
the security of one of those Gulf
countries. In the last few months, it's
been very sensitive. So obviously
there's going to be communication. We
communicate with multiple countries. You
know, if we post something about a
country, they might ask us questions,
etc. Some take it a step further. They
want to investigate us. I've had this
for years. Well, they were talking about
a topic and uh this was pretty common.
And then they put a just kind of throw a
word there. They're like, "We know
Mario, you know, is always worried about
someone spiking his drink and someone's
always watching it."
>> And I'm like, "So my executive said,
"Mario, they know everything about you.
They know everything. They told me they
told me things about you." They said
this. I'm like calling like for me, I've
got like kind of the Tucker approach
where I'm not hiding anything. And we've
just we've laughed about this before.
cuz if I am, it's going to come out. So,
I've just I live a life where if
everything comes out, you guys can
giggle about my life, but there's
nothing is going to bring me down and
there's nothing I'd be, you know, trying
to hide or trying too hard to hide. But
I'm like, how did they get this
particular piece of information? Cuz I
do. So, when I go out, I have security
and one of the main things my security
has to do is always watch my drink cuz
I'm paranoid someone will spike my
drink. I had it spiked last year.
>> Oh.
>> And I started vomiting. Yeah. I was at
an event. any so I always always watch
my drink and like they're the only ones
that know plus my loved one maybe my
brother and that's it no one else knows
about it like son of a did they go
to my security company and just ask them
cuz if they if a government is going to
reach out to my security guys and ask
them hey you have to share everything
the security guys are not going to say
no to the CIA of whatever country I'm
like son of a they went to my
security guys which are great people
[laughter] they're not with me anymore
they're different now but they're great
people and they went to They just got
like I read every single piece of
information about Mario Novel. It is
wild how they monitor everything. It is
wild. And it's not surprising to you,
but for people like me that are not from
this world. It's just crazy. And this is
like barely the tip of the iceberg. I
was You took the words right out of my
mouth. Just the tip of the iceberg. Look
at poor Glenn Greenwald. A year or so
ago, a video was leaked to try to
discredit him. And and to people's
credit, I mean, everybody from, you
know, Joe Nobody on Twitter all the way
up to Marjorie Taylor Green posted,
"Hey, Glenn, so sorry this happened. We
support you." You know, it's a it's from
the bag of dirty tricks. Yeah, that's
exactly what it was. It was a It was a
cheap and crude attempt to discredit
him.
>> Yeah. I It's two things on that. Number
one is Yes. And I was I was really I was
happy to see that because it was a
pretty embarrassing or at least in the
perception I for me I don't really care
but the average person might find it
embarrassing
>> and um and Glenn comes on the show I've
had him on the show many times. So it is
a pretty pretty embarrassing piece of
information and to see no one really I I
couldn't even imagine how Glenn would
feel. Poor guy. Poor guy. I think he's
married as well.
>> I felt awful for him.
>> And then to see that no one gave a
I'm like
yeah. If no one gives a
victory for Glenn,
>> I'm fine if everything of mine leaks,
I'm I'm I'm fine with that. So,
[laughter]
>> listen, I've been divorced twice. All my
shit's already out there. [laughter]
>> Already out there.
>> Um,
but it's it's that What do you make of
the Laura Loomer Ukraine thing?
I am not even vaguely in any way a Laura
Loomer fan. I woke up one Sunday a few
months ago to to a half a dozen emails
from friends saying, "Buddy, Laura
Loomer is just tearing you up on
Twitter." I was like, "What?"
>> Sorry, John. I want to interrupt. I
didn't know I was there. I was going to
talk about the Zilinsky interview, but
this is more exciting. She
>> tell me what happened. [laughter]
>> So, this has happened to me once before.
There was a woman, what was her name?
Let me look real quick. There was a
woman who went after me. Um
she was uh Louise Mench.
Uh she's a former British
parliamentarian
and she got divorced, married like
[clears throat]
AC/DC's road manager or Nirvana's road
manager or something like that. Moved to
the United States, divorced him, took
all his money, and all she does all day
long is just tweet. And she is like so
1,000%
pro- Ukraine. She's like irrational. She
also has a history of mental illness and
drug abuse. And so one night she just
decided to attack me. I've never met
this woman in my life. I've never had an
exchange with her in my life. And she
just attacked me. And so
in the words of a of an opposing divorce
attorney, John Kuryaku is a latigious
prick. And I called my lawyer and I
said, "Is this defamatory?" And he said,
"Yeah, it's defamatory." I said, "Then I
want to sue."
So, um, so we sent her a letter saying,
"We're going to sue unless you retract
everything." And she retracted
everything. She she had to pin an
apology for 6 months on her Twitter. Um,
but I won. So now Laura Loomer then
starts attacking me.
>> Laura, I'm just looking at Louise's I
just checked her on ex Louise Bag
Bagshaw.
>> Yes, Louise Bagshaw. Yes. Did she Did
she stop using the name Mench? M-n.
>> Yes. Her handle is Let me check. Yeah,
her head was Louise Mench, but her full
name on X is Louise Badshaw. But I've
got so many DMs from her. So, there's
something. She's chatting to my team
since 2020.
Yeah, since April 2024. I don't know
what it's about. Maybe it's nothing too
bad. Maybe she's threatened us or
blackmailed us. I don't know.
>> I'll check it later.
>> So, Laura Loomer, I wake up and Laura
Loomer's trying to tear me in. called me
a a Russian spy, a Russian asset, and a
common criminal. And it's like, okay.
So, I called the lawyer again. He's
like, you know what? He said, nobody
takes Laura Loomer seriously. She's a
nobody.
>> Like, she's literally the only person in
Donald Trump's circle that even Trump
thought was so crazy that she didn't
deserve a government job. And so, he
said, "Let it go." So, I let it go. And
like the very next day, she just moved
on to somebody else.
>> It was probably me. I got attacked by
her last two weeks ago for being I don't
know what I posted something and for
being a Muslim something about me I'm
not Muslim I was born Christian Orthodox
but about me being a Muslim something I
can't remember what it's about
completely forgot now I'm sure related
to Iran but um the reason I brought up
Laura Roomers is um the interview with
Zilinski and the reason I brought it up
with you is um just you're muted again
is the um part of a bigger question it
started with how many of these
influences in general do you think are u
are are paid off are compromised in one
way or another?
>> That's the question I wanted to ask you.
>> You know what? I actually think it's a
lot. I didn't even give this any thought
until about a year ago and there's an
investigative journalist whom I respect
a great deal and she said, "Listen, I've
had people independently tell me and she
named four podcasters that these four
podcasters are taking, for example, CIA
money." And I said, "Really?" I said,
"Boy, that would be pretty explosive.
Are you going to go public with it?" And
she said, "No, cuz I can't find anything
to confirm it." And there are four like,
you know, kind of household names that
she's under the impression take CIA
money. Well, if podcasters have taken
CIA money, you can bet your bottom
dollar they're taking Israeli money,
Russian money, maybe even Chinese money.
Who knows? Depending on what the issue
is. I could see it. And you know, Laura
Loomer, Laura Loomer,
it's funny when she was attacking me,
some guy, God bless him, total stranger,
he opened a new exac account just to
make this one tweet and then he canceled
it. He went to Grock and he said,
"Grock,
um,
who which country benefits the most from
what John Kiryaku says?" And then he put
it that I'm a whistleblower and torture
program. It says the United States and
it explains why. And then he said the
same words. What country most benefits
from Laura Loomer's statements. And then
it says Israel. And it has the whole
thing of her support for Israel. And
then he posted it and he canceled the
account. So I was like whoever it was,
thank you for defending me like that.
>> You should have you should have did it
go viral that post.
>> Jeez. I don't even know. You know, God
>> should have tweeted. There aren't enough
hours in the day for me to check these
things. But
>> but Laura Loomer has been all about
Russia, Russia, Russia, Russia since the
very beginning until now. And now it's
all about Ukraine. And I think that
she's at the point where she realizes
finally that she's not going to get a
job at the White House. She's not going
to be named the head of some obscure
federal agency somewhere. So she might
as well just, you know, worry about
Laura Loomer and do what's best for
Laura Loomer's followers. And I think
that for her, switching sides on Russia
Ukraine was the way to go.
>> Um, well, if Seb Gawker was able to get
a spot in the administration, John Laura
does have a does have a
>> God forbid. I've written about Seb
Gorka. Seb Gorka, for your viewers who
don't know, Dr. Sebastian Gorka is the
deputy national security adviser for
counterterrorism. But his father was a
Nazi. Not a Nazi sympathizer, not a
neo-Nazi. He was an actual Nazi from
Hungary. And Seb Gorka wears his
father's Nazi party lapel pin on his
suit and he says he's not a Nazi, but he
does it to honor his father because he
loved his father and that he's very
pro-Israel and he's Zionist and all this
stuff. Okay. Yeah, he's pro- Israel and
a Zionist, but it's still a Nazi party
lapel pin. So, what are you doing?
Everything that Donald Trump said there
in that clip is true. Everything he said
is true. So, let's break it down.
Benjamin Benjamin Netanyahu is is a
consumate uh politician. He's constantly
working on public opinion and he knows
that American public opinion, at least
on Israel and on Muslim countries, is is
easily
malleable. Right? All you have to do is
say Islam, terrorism, nuclear, and
everybody just runs around like their
hair is on fire. Um, Donald Trump knows
what he's doing because Trump is a
master of the media. Donald Trump is
terrific at manipulating the media. He
always has been. I can tell you when
when he used to have his show, The
Apprentice, I used to lay in bed with my
then wife and watch this show. And I
remember turning to her and saying, "You
know, I've got to admit, Trump has won
me over. I feel like I'm halfway through
an NBA just watching this show. He's
great at using the media."
So, he's right when he says, "Why does
BB have to say this to the public about
pickaxe mountain and we're going to bomb
them again and we're going to bomb them
into submission and they're an
existential threat to the United States
as well as to Israel?" Why say all that?
Because you're trying to influence
American public opinion to pressure the
president to do what you want him to do.
And I think Trump is tired of it. He's
tired of Netanyahu constantly trying to
manipulate him. And I want to make
another point, too, and this is going to
maybe be a little controversial,
but
we've all seen video of Netanyahu
speaking before Congress in 2002 and
saying, "Saddam Hussein is an
existential threat to Israel and to the
United States. if we overthrow Saddam
Hussein there will be peace in the
Middle East and then there wasn't and
then he's testifying before Congress in
2008 or 2009 and he says if we overthrow
Muar Gaddafi and the Libyan government
they're an existential threat to the
United States and to Israel we'll have
peace in the Middle East and we did that
and it just made everything worse and
then a year ago he's before Congress
saying if we overthrow the Iranian
government they're an existential threat
to the United States and to and to
Israel and will have peace in the Middle
East. No, we won't. We do all of
Israel's dirty work for it. We kill
thousands, tens of thousands of people.
And what do we get out of it? Nothing.
Well, I'll tell you what I think is a
little bit controversial. If you are the
leader of Iran or a leader of Iran,
what do you do to protect yourself? The
only thing that you can do is build a
nuclear weapon. We are not having a
conversation right now, for example,
about North Korea. You know why? Because
North Korea has a nuclear weapon. And so
nobody dares attack North Korea. Well,
if you're Iranian, the only thing you
can do to protect yourself from from
this ongoing war or any future war is to
develop a nuclear weapon.
And I think frankly that's the next
step. You can't bomb them forever. So
anyway, in this Trump quote, it's the
president of the United States telling
an ally, the the country's closest ally
maybe, you better not say anything to
the press first without running it by me
in public on a cable news hit. And let
me add one other thing. There was
something else that the president and
Netanyahu spoke about yesterday, and
that was the possible sale of F-35
fighter jets to Turkey. Now, the Greek
government and Greek Americans have long
been opposed to the sale of F-35s to
Turkey because, frankly, we're afraid
the Turks are going to use them against
Greece. Well, the Israelis are afraid
Israel. And so Netanyahu has been
strongly opposed to the sale of F-35s to
Turkey. He mentioned that in public
yesterday and the president didn't
appreciate it and he said, "I don't take
my orders from a foreign leader as to
which country I can make sales,
military sales to." And he meant it. It
was a slapdown to BB Netanyahu.
Something that we had we hadn't yet
seen. And I'll let you in on another
little secret. Presidents get caught
offguard by news all the time, even
about what their allies are doing or
have claimed they would do. They really
do not like hearing news from reporters
before getting it from the mouth of the
foreign leader. When that happens,
presidents usually fall back on
diplomatic stock phrases, things like,
"I don't discuss private conversations
with foreign leaders," or, "We're in
constant communication. The situation is
evolving." or any one of the other
100,000 phrases in the lexicon of
national security silliness and and
international diplomacy. Which is why it
is such a big deal that Trump chose to
reprimand Netanyahu for discussing
strategy with reporters rather than just
BS the question. You don't have to
answer every question a reporter throws
at you, especially when you know or
ought to know that your answer is going
to anger the president of the United
States. But BB right now is a very happy
man that he got this meeting at all. And
listen to this statement from
Netanyahu's communications director
about their relationship with Trump.
Here's what he said. quote, "There is no
truth in the claim that Israel is
pushing the US in a certain direction on
the Iran issue. The prime minister is
not telling the US president what to do
and is not pushing him in any direction.
You have to be utterly brain dead to
believe a single word of that. It's
actually offensive as an American and as
somebody who, you know, watches the news
even a little bit. It's offensive
that the Israeli prime minister's
communications director think any
American would believe that. Does that
sound like something you would say if
you were not pushing your friend in a
certain direction? Would you deny it
multiple times in a few sentences? Well,
after that little show from Netanyahu,
Trump told Fox News this morning,
"Excellent meeting." He said, "Be
understands now." So, apparently it was
enough. BB understands now. That tells
me that the president slapped him down.
What if the way money works is about to
change? Not someday, not hypothetically,
but right now. China and the United
States are both making moves that
suggest we could be heading towards
something the world hasn't seen in more
than 50 years. A return to goldbacked
money, or something very close to it.
China is shutting down paper gold
trading at four of its biggest banks all
on the same day. And they're building a
new system that settles in physical gold
instead. On our side, the government is
sitting on more than 8,000 tons of gold
still valued at $42 an ounce on the
books. Legislation to fix that is
already in Congress. If both superpowers
start anchoring their currencies to
gold, what happens to the price? And
more importantly, what happens to every
dollar in your retirement that isn't
backed by anything at all? That's the
question a free report from American
Alternative Assets answers. It's called
The Day Money Changes Forever. And if
you have an IRA or a 401k, you need to
read it right now. Get your free copy at
johnlovesgold.com.
That's johnlovesgold.com
or call 888G053.
Well, I started this episode by saying
that there was a lot of news to get
through and there is a lot of news. We
just didn't think yesterday when we
started putting this together that so
much of it would be focused on Israel,
but here we are. Let's talk about
Netanyahu and the International Criminal
Court. I want to show you something else
that's disturbing. We have given Lindsey
Graham a lot of airtime on the show the
last two weeks, but I truly cannot think
of a more revealing person as far as how
Benjamin Netanyahu captured US officials
and anyone sympathetic to his cause.
Last night, we got some crocodile tears
from Netanyahu about how difficult the
International Criminal Court is
potentially making his life. After all,
he's been charged with war crimes and
crimes against humanity. Let's listen to
what Sean Hannity had to say.
>> But it scares me in this sense for you.
Um, you travel internationally.
>> Yeah.
>> God forbid you had a medical emergency
and you need to land and you're you're
about to land in a country that
recognizes the ICC. It could complicate
things. Do you worry about that?
>> Yeah, I think about it. You know, we
have uh we have special forces around.
you know, I served with them for 5
years. No,
>> the IDF is pretty tough. They have a
very
>> Let's give them a new task, you know.
Yeah, of course. It's Look, it's the
corruption of the international system.
It's an unelected unelected bureaucracy
that sits in the H
could arrest American soldiers because
you don't recognize this corrupt body
any more than we do. And they could say
that the president of the United States
is a war criminal. That uh American
soldiers valiantly fighting next to us,
shoulderto-shoulder against these the
tyranny and tan that they're war
criminals. They could pick them up.
>> Man, there's so much to talk about here.
The United States and Israel are not
signitories to what's called the Rome
Statute. The Rome Statute created the
ICC and made it something akin to what
we had at Nuremberg after the Second
World War where Nazi war criminals were
given a fair trial. Some were acquitted
and others were convicted, some were
executed, some were imprisoned. But
there ought to be an international
agreement that when somebody commits war
crimes or somebody commits crimes
against humanity that they're dealt
with. Right? Look at Sloban Mallich, the
former dictator of Yugoslavia. He died
in a prison cell in the HEG as he should
have.
But the United States doesn't recognize
the ICC and Israel doesn't recognize the
ICC. And so Netanyahu is free to come
and go from the United States as he
pleases and he comes many times a year.
But what happens if he has a medical
emergency on a flight? What happens if
the plane has engine trouble and it's
forced to land in Italy, Austria,
Greece, Spain,
wherever, Ireland,
the leaders of those countries are
compelled by treaty to arrest him and to
turn him over to the ICC. Okay. What
would happen in in that event? Well,
Congress has already thought about what
would happen. During the Obama
administration, Congress passed
something known as the HEG Invasion Act,
which authorizes the president
to call out the US military to invade
the Netherlands,
to invade the Netherlands,
and to take over the International
Criminal Court to then free Benjamin
Netanyahu and let him run back to
Israel. This is how crazy the world has
gotten. Now, when Netanyahu talks about
unelected bureaucrats, you know, yeah,
that's the way the world works. Every
country has unelected bureaucrats.
That's how governments operate.
Who elected the Nermberg tribunal?
Nobody. They were appointed by the
United States, Britain, France, and the
Soviet Union. And it worked. It showed
that rule of law is really a thing that
needs to be respected.
I've said multiple times in multiple
venues, you cannot have your policy
be to just go into some place like Gaza
or the West Bank and kill everybody,
men, women, children, the elderly. You
flatten the hospitals, you flatten the
flatten the homes, you flatten the
schools, and then whoever survives, you
starve them. Those are war crimes and
crimes against humanity. And sure, the
United States, which I believe strongly,
is wrong on this issue. The United
States is going to save you. But most
other countries aren't. They aren't
going to save you.
Yesterday,
we got another bombshell. This is
Netanyahu strategizing with Lindsey
Graham about how to discredit the ICC
when they came out with their ruling
that Netanyahu had likely committed war
crimes. Listen to this. It's Lindsey
Graham on the phone with Netanyahu.
>> So basically they're going to have a
street
opponent of making the decision very
soon. Is possible to have to appeal to
uh the court to say, "Okay, we want to
review this." Before you do anything,
there has to be a review about this
entire process. I understand that you
sent a letter
with maybe with some other senators. I
don't know if you got any Democrat.
>> I I tell you the perfect person would be
the speaker. Speaker Johnson
>> would be what?
>> Speaker Johnson.
>> No, to have to have him on the letter.
>> Yeah, sure. Sure you would.
I don't know. I won't know to try. But I
will try. I promise you that.
>> So, let's let's unpack that. Did you
catch how casual their tone was? Uh, let
me brainstorm some Democrats we can get
to cosign. And of course, there will be
or there would have been Democrats.
Netanyahu there is talking exactly like
how he would say say call a friend if a
judge were to find him guilty of a
crime. No plan.
desperate for anything. I'm going to
call my friend Lindsay, see if Lindsay
can write a strongly worded letter, get
a bunch of important people to sign it,
and um
hope for the best. What else are you
going to do? Let me read for you the
rest of that reporting from the New York
Times because it's it's shocking. You're
going to want to hear it. Quote, "Mr.
Holder recorded the audio without video
of a second call between the two men
that he said took place later that day.
Only Mr. Graham's voice could be heard.
On that call, Mr. Graham joked to Mr.
Netanyahu that he should quote, "pay me
for all this. I should get tons of
shekels," unquote. "It would take more
than dinner," unquote, he added. Then he
said that quote, "We got them both,"
unquote, appearing to refer to senators
Richard Blumenthal of Connecticut and
Ben Carden of Maryland, two Democrats
who said they would sign a letter
protesting the efforts to move ahead
with an arrest warrant. Quote, "So
here's why I'm calling you," Mr. Graham
told Mr. Netanyahu, saying that he hoped
to get the letter, quote, "Out the door
Wednesday,"
unquote, appearing to refer to the next
day, October 30th. quote, "So send me
over whatever you want to say, and they
want to say two things to the ICC,"
unquote. One was that the prosecutor
should speak with the Israeli government
and not move ahead with the case until,
quote, the cloud is lifted, unquote,
from the prosecutor's own problems. What
Mr. Graham requested in exchange, he
said, was for Mr. Netanyahu quote to
call Blumenthal and Cardon and thank
them for being fairminded on this and
also thank them for trying to help with
Saudi Israel normalization. You
appreciate it. You're very interested in
it and that will encourage both of
them."
The letter was released on November 1st,
2024, and it included Mr. Blumenthal and
Mr. Cardon as signers in addition to
noting the allegations against Mr. Khan,
the prosecutor who just resigned a week
ago because of sexual improprieties. The
letter said that the ICC
quote did not comply unquote with the
law by declining to keep a planned
meeting with Israeli representatives
before applying for their arrest
warrant. None of them responded for
comment.
Um, I'm very sensitive
to the term espionage.
Um, I mentioned in a previous episode
that in my case, my judge set a new
legal precedent for application of the
Espionage Act and she determined that
espionage was very simply providing
national defense information to any
person not entitled to receive it.
Simple.
None of these documentary filmmakers
were cleared for classified information.
And literally everything that Lindsey
Graham is talking about is classified.
People in the United States have gone to
prison for far less collusion with a
foreign leader than what he we have seen
in these tapes, these videos of Lindsey
Graham and Benjamin Netanyahu.
And it also leads me to ask
where in the world America's
relationship with Israel is heading.
Where will it be in 5 10 30 years?
I mentioned in the last five there's
been a 50 percentage point split or move
away from support for Israel.
And now the vast majority of Democrats,
the vast majority of independents and a
sizable number of Republicans
think that Benjamin Netanyahu committed
war crimes and that he should be
prosecuted. Have you ever wondered what
it feels like to shoot with the same
precision tech used by US special
forces? Well, good news. After years of
research and development, MCG Tackle
just dropped something incredible. The
Stinger combat site. This is not your
average red dot. Using holographic
technology once reserved for elite
military and law enforcement, the
Stinger delivers crystalclear precision,
so accurate that you could hit a dime at
300 yards without even trying. This is
the exact same level of technology used
by the pros. But here's the twist. Most
sites like this go for 600 bucks or
more, and people happily pay it. But
right now, through an exclusive deal
with MCG Tactical, you can get this
milspec site for under $200. And it gets
better. From my listeners, you're
getting 67% off and they're covering
shipping. You know, I talk all the time
about not yet having my gun rights back.
It's something that my attorneys and I
are working on, but I am still a regular
at gun shows in the Washington DC area,
and I can tell you that there are
different sites out there. There are
different lasers and red dots that you
can look at. Nothing nothing is as good
as this. So, just scan the QR code or go
to mcgac.com/jsting
to get yours today. The only catch,
supply is tight and these are already
flying off the shelves. So, if you want
a site built for the best, now's your
chance. Grab yours before they have to
shut down orders. That is
mcgac.com/jhsting.
Well, welcome to a new segment that we
are going to call the profile. When I
was in the CIA, it used to be my job. It
was my very first job in the CIA to to
profile foreign leaders for the
president, the vice president, the
national security adviser, and the
secretaries of state and defense.
anytime they were seeing a world leader,
we had to write a classified
psychological profile of that world
leader. And I still kind of enjoyed
doing it just for myself.
My job at the agency when I first got
hired was uh to be essentially Saddam
Hussein's classified biographer for the
intelligence community, his his
classified psychological biographer. and
I worked with a team of psychiatrists,
psychologists, and anthropologists to
make sure that that we had cutting edge
analysis.
Well, our first profile is going to be
on a man named Raza Palavi, someone who
also attended Lindsey Graham's funeral
yesterday in Washington. Raza Pali is a
former crown prince and the eldest son
of the last Sha of Iran.
He's been waiting in the wings
attempting to jockey to lead Iran in the
event of regime change.
You're going to hear how charismatic he
is in these clips. And you can make your
own decision as to how likely it is that
he's going to be the leader of Iran. But
let me say a couple of things about Raza
Pali. Um I not so jokingly have referred
to him in podcast appearances in the
past as the clown prince of Iran.
He left Iran as a very young man in his
very early 20s or about the age of 20 in
1979.
He hasn't been back to Iran since 1979.
He is strongly supported by Israel uh by
the Jewish community here in America, by
the Iranian exile community here in
America. not the entire community, but I
mean like the Southern California, very
wealthy uh Iranian exiles.
He lives in a multi-million dollar
palace in PTOIC, Maryland, a close-end
suburb of Washington DC,
but he's not a player. He's never been a
player since the US and Israel began
bombing Iran. He's appeared on a handful
of podcasts. He was on the Patrick Bet
David show uh once or twice and a couple
of other podcasts
in which he sort of says what you would
expect him to say that you know yes the
regime is terrible it has to be
overthrown the Iranian people have to be
liberated and then sometimes he'll say
that he's the one who should lead Iran
and other times he says that he's not
the one who should lead Iran. The truth
is he and I've I've said this in the
past and I've gotten death threats for
it. I'm going to say it again. He would
not survive the walk from the plane to
the terminal if he were to go back to
Iran. Nobody wants him in Iran. Nobody.
And if there's one thing that the
Israeli and American bombing of Iran
has done
is that it's united the Iranian people.
You can't
you can't attack a country, murder its
religious leader, murder most of its
senior governmental leadership, murder
all of its military leaders, murder all
of its nuclear scientists, and say, "We
are here to help.
We know we've been bombing you and we
the first night of the bombing we blew
up the school and killed 160s something
little girls from a school. But but we
are the good guys and we're here to help
you. And we want to take this stoogge,
this clown from PTOIC, Maryland, and
impose him on you so that he can be a
dictator like his father was.
Well, the reason that that Raza Palab's
father, Muhammad Raalvi, was overthrown
in the first place is because he was a
bloodthirsty, murderous dictator,
and people were tired of being murdered
by the Savak, the secret police.
So, Raza Palv is not going back to Iran.
He's not going to lead Iran. He's not
going to be a player in any respect.
Although
the pro-war faction of the Republican
party
and the Israeli government think he's
great. We've got a little clip that we
want to show you of an interview that
Raza Palvi did yesterday with Reuters.
There have been reports and they're kind
of anonymous that you've received
funding from Israel and Saudi Arabia. Is
that true?
>> Absolutely false. I have not been a
recipient of any governmental or public
fund on the outside. Every dime that
comes to my campaign comes from private
donations of supporters. Hopefully,
we'll have more benefactors that'll give
us bigger checks.
>> From where we're sitting today, when do
you think regime change might occur?
>> I think we're very close to it. And the
reason I say this is because first and
foremost, the regime is at its weakest
it's ever been since 47 years. Not to
mention the fact that in terms of
legitimacy, it has totally lost any
remaining possible legitimacy it might
have had.
That's just wrong. He's just wrong. He
forgets that when his father was first
overthrown, Iran went through a series
of presidents. There was even an
editorial cartoon at the time I remember
in the New York Times where Ayatollah
Humeni was telling some Iranian-looking
guy, I have good news and I have bad
news. The good news is I'm naming you
president of Iran. The bad news is I'm
naming you president of Iran.
Because there was a cycle of presidents
of Iran that would just get blown up or
shot or arrested or disappeared or
whatever. That was when the regime was
weak.
Not today. This war has forced the
Iranian populace together to rally. You
know, you would think that we would have
learned a lesson with the Iraq war.
We have so convinced ourselves that
we're the good guys. We just can't
fathom the notion that when we cross a
border, we're not going to be seen as
liberators. were going to be seen as
invaders and occupiers. It happens time
and time again. We couldn't defeat the
Taliban. They didn't even have shoes
and they beat us. We couldn't defeat uh
the Iraqis. Iraq is still in a state of
chaos. But we think that we're going to
be greeted in as liberators in Iran. Why
would we think that? We would think that
because people don't have any
understanding of history.
So, here is this clown waiting in the
wings pretending to jockey to lead Iran
in the event of regime change.
Well, I would liken him to Ahmed Chelby.
For those of you who don't remember
Ahmed Chelby, he was a similar clown
that was in the pay of the CIA, the
American government. and we made this
really stupid plan to make him the
president of Iraq as soon as we
overthrew Saddam Hussein and the Iraqi
people said, "Oh, no you don't."
Well, it's happening again. Finally, one
of the things that the Iranian
government has been really good at since
the start of this war is propaganda.
I enjoy looking at pieces of propaganda
because some of them are really great
and some of them are really terrible.
I've told the story a couple of times
about my last visit to Yemen in 2011. I
met with the US defense attache in the
American embassy in SA and I asked him
kind of off-handedly, so what are you
working on? What's new? And he said, oh,
we've got this wonderful SCOP
psychological operation. It's a
propaganda operation. I said, oh, cool.
What are you doing? and he said, "We've
created a pirate radio station and we're
broadcasting jazz
across Yemen and then at the end of each
hour you can call in and talk about the
jazz."
I said, "Why would you do that?"
Well, it's going to make people like
jazz and they know that jazz is American
and so that'll make them like America.
How'd that work out for us?
Jazz in Yemen.
There's not enough food. People are
literally starving to death. They're
constantly at war, if not with each
other, with Saudi Arabia and now with
everybody else.
But they're going to listen to jazz and
call the propaganda station to talk
about how great the jazz is.
Well, the Iranians are not making jazz
stations. They're making Lego
animations. And these Lego animations
are fantastic. Let's take a look at the
latest one.
>> You [music] started the war. You thought
you would win. Uh-huh. Now look at the
mess that your country is in. Look at
it. Your general's crying. Your plan was
a [music] bust. The promises [singing]
made turn into dust. Marco Rubio was
sweating. He's grilled on the floor.
They asked for the billions you wasted
on war. You lied from day one. [music]
You keep capping a lot. But look at the
street. Yeah, we got it on lock down.
Begging for mercy. You're begging for
peace while telling your media [music]
cease. You sure
you're losing the straight. You're
losing the state. And now the whole
public is drowning in you. Stop talking
about Epstein. Now listen to the crowd.
FC [music]
>> louder
F
>> don't stop talking about
>> X F
>> louder [music]
F
>> you lied about your own
>> that is very sophisticated
the purpose of it is not to convince
Americans to switch sides and you know
side with Iran although that would be a
benefit that the Iranian regime I think
would would appreciate.
It's to influence everybody else in
between European public opinion, really
broader world public opinion. Um, the
Iranians have produced at least a half a
dozen of these and each one is more
creative than than the previous one.
Now, compare that to some of the
propaganda that we see from other
countries. Not the American stupid jazz
idea, but let's say from the Russians.
You know, the Democrats were adamant
that the Russians tried to steal the
2016 election for Donald Trump. That
turned out to be untrue. And in fact,
the Russian government spent $50,000 on
Facebook advertising. But 25,000 of the
50,000 was spent after the election was
over. And the remaining 25,000 was spent
in states that were already either
solidly blue or solidly red. And what
was that propaganda?
It was
pictures of kittens and puppies and
flowers and then the occasional mention
of, you know, politics.
Big deal. It was a failure. The Chinese
are no better. And it's because the
Chinese don't really understand American
culture and we don't really feel a
connection to Chinese culture because
most of us are, you know, of European uh
origin or South American, Latin American
origin or African origin, not East Asian
origin. And so the the thought process
is different when it comes to
propaganda. But this from the Iranians
is very sophisticated
and they're going to keep coming out
with more of them in order to influence
college students, let's say, or working
people
mostly in Europe
and to get them to separate themselves
from the US and Israel. It's something
that really bears watching.
Folks, I wanted to thank you again for
your embrace of this uh this podcast. I
have to say I'm I'm speechless when I I
look at the numbers each day. I make a
joke when I do cameos that if it wasn't
for you and people like you, I would be
living in the backseat of my car at the
Walmart parking lot over in Fairfax,
Virginia.
But that's only kind of a half a joke
for me. Like my sister, God bless her,
my sister's my best friend. And my
sister always says, "No, you would live
with me." And I'm like, "Yeah, I'm I'd
be an old man living in my sister's
basement." But in all seriousness, it's
only because of you that we're able to
do this and that we're able to keep it
going as an ongoing concern. So, thank
you for watching. Thank you for your
emails and your questions. Thank you for
liking and sharing and subscribing. It
really means the world to us and we're
going to keep it going because you like
it and we like doing